Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research files, 1975; 1959-2000; MS2001 Series 4; 59.5 Linear Feet 113 document boxes, 3 flat boxes
  - General, 1982-1983
    - Maryland Families Conference, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Mathias, Charles, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 27)
    - Mauritania, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - May, Catherine, 1968-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 28)
    - McCarthy, Charles, 1954; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 16)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 17)
    - McCarthy, Joseph, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 18)
    - McClellan, John, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 29)
    - McCloskey, Paul, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 19)
    - McCord, James, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 20)
    - McCormack, John [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 312, Folder 21)
    - McCormack, John [2 of 2], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 30)
    - McGovern, George, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - McGovern, George - Chapman's Friend Reports, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 2, Box R6, Folder 9)
    - McIntyre, Thomas, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 31)
    - McMillan, John [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - McMillan, John [2 of 2], 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 432, Folder 32)
    - McNamara, Robert, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Meat standards, 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Medellin Cartel, 1966-1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Media, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Medical care, 1977-1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Medical research, 1962-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Medicare, 1984-1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Men not in office, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Mengele, Josef, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Meridian Hill Park, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Metromedia, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Mexico, 1957-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Miami Beach scandal, 1979-1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Middle East, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Middle East disarmament, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Migrant workers, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Military Posture, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 8, Box R6, Folder 10)
    - Military strategy, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Militia movement, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Miller, William, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Mills, Wilbur, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Minerals Management Service, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Mink, Patsy, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Minshall, William, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 3)
    - Misinformation, 1969-1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Missile and rocket systems, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R6, Folder 11, Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Mitchell, John, 1971-1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell deposition, 1976-1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell/Chotiner memos, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 3, Box R6, Folder 12)
    - Mobil Oil, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Mollenhoff, Clark, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Moller, Jan - research, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Mondale, Walter, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Monroe, Marilyn, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 443, Folder 3)
    - Monroney, Mark, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Arch, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Gordon, 1984-1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 7)
    - Morality, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Morgan, Elizabeth, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R6, Folder 13, Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Morse, Wayne, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 8)
    - Morton, Rogers, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 9)
    - Mosley, David, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Moss, Frank, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 10)
    - Mott, Stewart, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Mounted documents re: China and Pakistan, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R13, Folder 1)
    - Muhammad, Elijah, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Multer, Abraham, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 11)
    - Murder Will Out, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - Murphy, George, 1972; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 12)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - Muskie, Edmund, 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 315, Folder 14)
    - Nard, Jack, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - NASA, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - National Archives, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - National Credit Union Administration, 1971-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - National Football League, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - National Park Service, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - National Rifle Association, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 459, Folder 6)
    - National Security Council, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - National Security Memo - Covert action, 1968-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 1, Box 316, Folder 10)
    - National Youth Alliance, 1989-1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Native Americans, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Native Americans, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 13)
    - NATO, 1965-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 2, Box 316, Folder 14)
    - Natural gas, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 15)
    - Navy, 1960-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 16)
    - Nazis, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 17)
    - Nazi underground - South America, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 18)
    - Nelson, Gaylord, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 13)
    - Nelson, Terry, 1963-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 316, Folder 19)
    - Neo-Nazis, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Nepotism, 1972-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Neuberger, Maurine, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - New Latin Casino, 1952-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Newman, Barbara, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Niarchos, Stavros, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Nicaragua, 1957-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Nickerson, Col. John, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Nixon, Don, 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Pat, 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 10)
    - Nixon, Richard [1 of 3], 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 317, Folder 11)
    - Nixon, Richard [2 of 3], 1969-1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Nixon, Richard [3 of 3], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Nixon, Richard - the press, 1950-1952; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Nixon, Richard - women, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Nixon slush fund, 1987-1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Nixon - taxes, 1987-1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - North, Oliver [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - North, Oliver [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - North Korea, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - November Group, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear materials, 1966-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear power, 1973-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 12)
    - Nuclear power plants, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 13)
    - Nuclear waste, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 318, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear weapons [1 of 2], 1980-1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 1, Box R7, Folder 3)
    - Nuclear weapons [2 of 2], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - October Surprise, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 4, Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Offensive weapons in Cuba, 1980-1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 5, Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1973-1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Office of Management and Budget, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Oil [1 of 2], 1956-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Oil [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 8, Box R7, Folder 6)
    - Oil and gas [1 of 2], 1966-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Oil and gas [2 of 2], 1966-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Oil- energy crisis [1 of 2], 1964-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Oil- energy crisis [2 of 2], 1967-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 12)
    - Oil lobby, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 13)
    - Oil shale, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 319, Folder 14)
    - O'Konski, Alvin, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 14)
    - Onassis, Aristotle, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy [1 of 2], 1968-1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy [2 of 2], 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Organized crime, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Otepka, Otto, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Ottinger, Richard, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 15)
    - Ox-Bow incident, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Pakistan, 1972-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Palestine Liberation Organization, 1996-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Panama, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Panama, 1968-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Parade article ideas, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 11)
    - Parade story ideas, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 12)
    - Parade Magazine article research, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 13)
    - Parade Magazine - National Bulletin Board, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 14)
    - Paraga, Dobroslav, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 15)
    - Passman, Otto E., undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 16)
    - Pastore, John [1 of 2], 1965-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 16)
    - Pastore, John [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 17)
    - Patman, Wright [1 of 2], 1973-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 320, Folder 17)
    - Patman, Wright [2 of 2], 1994; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 18)
    - Patriotism, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Payne, L.F. / Landrith, George, 1959-1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Peanut program, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Pearson, Drew [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Pearson, Drew [2 of 2], 1995-1996; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 19)
    - Pearson, Drew - research, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Pedicle screws, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Pensions, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Pentagon, 1961; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Pepper, Claude, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 20)
    - Pepsi Co., Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Pergamon Press, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Persian Gulf, 1964-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Perspectives on Security and Strategy in the 1980s, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - Pharmaceuticals, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 13)
    - Phillipines, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 14)
    - Phillipines - Communism, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 15)
    - Physically handicapped, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 16)
    - Pike, Otis G., undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 21)
    - Plasmapheresis, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 17)
    - Poff, Richard H., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 22)
    - Poland, 1967-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 18)
    - Police - St. George, Utah, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 321, Folder 19)
    - Pollution, 1973-1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Polygamy, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Pornography, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Pornography restrictions, 1965-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Post Office jobs, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Postal Service, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1967-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Presidential election - 1972, 1961-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - President's Council on Youth Opportunity, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - Presidents, Senators, and Governors, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - President's Task Force on Private Sector Initiatives, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 11, Box R7, Folder 7)
    - Presidential campaigns, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 12)
    - Presidential election - 1980, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 13)
    - Presidential election - 1984, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 14)
    - Presidential election - 1988, 1968-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 15)
    - Presidential promises, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 16)
    - Presidio, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 17)
    - The Press, 1971-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 18)
    - Pressler, Larry, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 19)
    - Prisons, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 20)
    - Profiles of congressmen (notecards), 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 23)
    - Project on Military Procurement, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 21)
    - Project Mudhen (Anderson surveillance by CIA), Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 8, Box 322, Folder 22)
    - Proxmire, William, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 322, Folder 23)
    - Psychic warfare, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Psychological operations in guerrilla warfare, 1979-1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Pulitzer nomination, 1979-1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Qaddafi, Muammar [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Qaddafi, Muammar [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Quayle, Dan, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Quie, Albert, 1974-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Quotes, 1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Radiation, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - Radziwill, Lee, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Railroads, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Rasband, Judith, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Ray, James Earl, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Rayburn Building, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - Reader's Digest v. Marin County, 1966-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 15)
    - Reagan, Nancy, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 16)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 17)
    - Reagan, Ronald, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 18)
    - Reagan, Ronald - assassination attempt, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 323, Folder 19)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 1-101, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 102-218, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 219-333g, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 334-466, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 467-612, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 613-771, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 446, Folder 6)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 772-950, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 951-1083, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - The Real Thing by Joseph Valachi, pp. 1084-1180 [end], 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - Redburn, Max - Brigham Young University, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Reform, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Refuseniks, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Reid, Charlotte T., Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Reid, Harry, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Reid, Ogden R., 1990-1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Religion, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Religious liberty, 1971-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Remote viewing, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Republican Party, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Republican political action plan, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Resnick, Joseph Y., Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 12)
    - Reynolds, Don, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 13)
    - Rhodes, John, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 15)
    - Richardson, Elliot, 1962-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 16)
    - Rickover, Hyman, 1961-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 17)
    - The Right, 1961-1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 324, Folder 18)
    - Right wing [1 of 2], 1961-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Right wing [2 of 2], 1968-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Right wing infiltration, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Right-wing literature, 1966-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Rights of homemakers, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Rivers, Mendel, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [1 of 7], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [2 of 7], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [3 of 7], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [4 of 7], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [5 of 7], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [6 of 7], 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Robertson ("Pat") v. McCloskey [7 of 7], 1963-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller family [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller family [2 of 2], 1962; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Rodgers, Will, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Romney, George, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Rooney, John L., 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Roselli, John, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Roxby, James, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Roudebush, Richard, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Russia, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - Sachs, Stephen H., 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 11)
    - Salinger, Pierre, 1968-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 12)
    - SAM-6 missiles, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 13)
    - Samoa, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 14)
    - Saudi Arabia [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 9, Box 327, Folder 15)
    - Saudi Arabia [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 16)
    - Saudi Arabia - foreign investments, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 327, Folder 17)
    - Savings and loan scandal, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Savings and loans, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Saylor, John P., 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Schwarzkopf, Norman, 1973-1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Schweiker, Richard, 1950-1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Scoops, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Scoops, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 7)
    - Secret negotiations - SALT, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 8, Box R7, Folder 10)
    - Secret Service, 1965-1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Secret Service - administrative profiles, 1972-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R7, Folder 11, Box 328, Folder 10)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 11)
    - Security classifications, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 12)
    - Selden, Armistead I., Jr., Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 13)
    - Select Committee on Intelligence - U.S. Senate, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 14)
    - Senate Commerce Committee, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 15)
    - Senate Committee on Governmental Affairs, 1963-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 16)
    - Senate Committee on Government Operations, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 17)
    - Senate ethics, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 18)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee - Arms Control, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 19, Box R7, Folder 12)
    - Senate Judiciary Committee, 1973-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 20)
    - Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 21, Box R7, Folder 13)
    - Sexism, 1977-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 22)
    - Sexual harassment, 1977-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 328, Folder 23)
    - Shah of Iran [1 of 2], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 329, Folder 1, Box R7, Folder 14)
    - Shah of Iran [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Shapp, Gov. Milton, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 329, Folder 3)